["I Got That Hello" playing]
♪I got that boom pow
I make it freaky wild ♪
♪ I’m making up my own style ♪
♪ I got that hey hi, I got that hello
I've got it ♪
♪ Hey hey hey
I got that good stuff… ♪
[Chrishell] Oh my God, this is so cool.
When this house hit the market,
we knew we had to see it in person.
It looked so crazy in the photos.
A bunch of us just have given it
the moniker of the Versace house,
just because
there's so much Versace in the house:
wallpaper, glasses, dishes,
all these things that I never even knew
that Versace made.
So, call me, Donatella.
-[Mary] Hi!
-[Chrishell] Hi! How are you?
-Good timing. Wow, this is so rand.
-[Amanza] You guys look so cute.
[Chrishell] Oh God. Beautiful to see.
Being a good agent,
we're always trying to think about
if we have the buyer for this house
when we go and tour the property, but…
obviously, we also just want
to see it for ourselves.
-Hi, I'm Chrishell. How are you?
-Hi. Ivana. Hi, nice to meet you.
This is actually built in '98,
it's completely remodeled.
The current owner bought it two years ago.
Look around.
Let me know if you have any questions.
[Chrishell] Okay, thank you.
♪ I wanna be rich, be rich ♪
-We match today, I see.
-[Mary] Oh my God, we do!
Did you call each other?
-No, but I love it!
-I'm the outcast.
-Wait, you didn't get the memo?
-Didn't get the memo.
-[Mary] Oh, wow.
-[Chrishell] Wait, look, there's a zipper.
-[Amanza, Mary] I know.
-[Mary] So cool.
-[Amanza] Let's go to the kitchen.
-Okay. You wanna go?
-[Chrishell] I love these bar stools.
-I do too. Everything is immaculate..
-[Mary] Yeah.
-I know. I feel like for nine million,
that would be how much it would cost just
for the furniture and the Versace stuff.
[Amanza] And the couch,
this Bentley sofa, like--
-I didn't know they made those.
-[Mary] It's insane.
The client that buys this house,
they have silk Versace jumpsuit, like,
Versace sunglasses,
they're driving their Bentley.
Probably have mistresses and pool boys,
and I don't even know what.
But, it's definitely
not for your average person.
-[Amanza] Is this all Versace wallpaper?
-[Ivana] It's Versace wallpaper.
-[Chrishell gasps] Wow. Cool.
-[Amanza] So stinkin' cute.
-[Chrishell] I'm gonna sit on it.
-[Mary] I know! I'm like, I wanna sit!
-Alright, let's watch Mean Girls.
-[all laugh]
-[Amanza] Oh, boy.
-[Mary] Make some popcorn.
[Chrishell] Amanza,
I haven't seen you in forever.
-I know.
-You were missed at the Friendsgiving.
-[Mary] I know.
-How'd it go with everybody?
-There was a lot of people there.
-It went well. Great food…
So they're catering
my charity event on Thursday.
-[Mary] Perfect.
-[Amanza] That's awesome!
Which reminds me, what are we supposed to…
bring or do for that?
If you wanna come a little early
and help me set up,
-that would be awesome.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-[Chrishell] Really?
-[all laugh]
-[Mary] Tell Amanza a couple hours early…
-And she'll be on time.
What time? Just tell Mary what time
and then tell me three hours before that.
I'll be there.
I can help the stagers
if they need extra hands.
Maybe bring some comfortable shoes
and we can change into our fancy shoes
for the event.
[Amanza] Perfect.
-Oh! Is this a real zebra? Feels like it.
-[Amanza] Oh, I hope not.
-[Mary] Really?
-Not anymore.
You have to catch me up. What is going on
with the court stuff and the kids?
Everything okay?
Well, we went. Mary went with me.
So we started the process.
There's, like, one more step,
and then they'll be mine.
That's exciting.
[Amanza] Yeah.
Getting custody of my kids is bittersweet.
But it feels good
to get the paperwork part over with
and just move forward.
We should go hang out by the pool
before they close on it.
[Chrishell] I wanna see.
[Amanza] Oh, it feels good out here.
This is so nice.
Well, you go that way, I'll go this way.
Oh yeah, you guys do that,
and I'm gonna stand above.
Penelope, it's time for my morning tea.
[Amanza, Mary laugh]
Chrishell's like, "Ya'll got any lemonade
or sweet tea in there?"
[accent] Well, shit!
[laughs] I'd reckon you'd fit in real nice
right here, wouldn't you?
That's right. You can put boots
in the oven, it don't make 'em biscuits.
What?
[Chrishell] I want to come down
to the pool with you guys.
[Mary] Yeah, come down here. You've got
to see the house from this angle.
You look like a movie star.
And Miss Kentucky, number 34,
Chrishell Hartley.
I would like world peace.
[all laugh]
Then you don't wanna work
at the Oppenheim Group.
[Mary] Oh, Gosh.
Oh my gosh. Wow.
This would be a good place--
-…Christine would live in.
-Yeah.
[Amanza] Is Christine coming
to your event?
-[Chrishell] Yeah. We're all good now.
-Speaking of Christine.
Yeah?
[Mary] She called me
and wants to talk.
-[Chrishell] That's never good.
-I know. We've kinda been
at odds for a while? I don't need to have
a talk with her. She needs to…
-[Amanza] Like, back off my best friend.
-Chill.
-[Amanza] That is so stupid.
-Oh my God.
I'm just… I'm so sick of her, like,
stirring up shit.
She prances in in her fancy outfits
and makes a joke. She thinks it's okay.
And it's not. I'm sick of it.
It's bullshit. Like…
I got a ponytail too, girl.
[Amanza] Flip it.
-[Chrishell] I do too, today!
-[Mary laughs]
[Chrishell] Oh…
-Well, I do but it doesn't work.
-Mary's is like a bunny tail.
I got a little nub.
You've got style,
you've got a great weave.
I do have style. If I had all that money
I'd be dressed like that too, shit.
Let me sell a 40 million dollar house.
Let's go.
♪ It's a brand new day ♪
♪ It's a new day, let's just show
Suck it up, time to celebrate ♪
♪ Let your wild out, make the world know
You've arrived, you're alive ♪
♪And it's about to blow… ♪
[Heather] So excited!
I know that you
would love and appreciate this,
-so that's why I asked you to come.
-My god, yes!
-Thank you, babe. Is this it?
-Yay!
♪ Come on, turn it up
It's a new day… ♪
[Christine] I love a good
wedding dress shopping day.
-Oh my. This is gorgeous.
-Hi, how are you?
-Hi, I'm Kara, great to meet you.
-Welcome. Congratulations.
-Hi, I'm Heather, nice to meet you.
-Hi. Great to meet you.
Welcome to Galia Lahav.
-Gorgeous.
-Thank you. Have you given any thought
to a particular style or look
that you're interested in?
Yeah. I think I'm gonna do
one dress for the wedding
-that's super over-the-top, super long.
-Awesome.
And I do wanna change dress.
-Okay. So you do want a second look.
-I definitely-- Yeah.
-Whoever said I don't want two dresses--
-Absolutely.
Who doesn't wanna wear couture twice?
Exactly.
-You need two.
-Fantastic.
I'm not doing a white dress.
Okay, perfect.
What's your color preference?
It's gonna be black.
Oh, black. [gasps]
Wow, that's so… interesting.
That's amazing. We've never
really done anything like that.
-Have you done that, or is she the first?
-Has anyone ever done that before?
We do a lot of custom orders,
but never in black. So exciting.
-[Kara] We'll start to pull some of these.
-[Christine] Perfect.
I found Galia Lahav
through my event planner.
The thing I love about her dresses
is they're so sexy, they're so well done.
I've always considered myself
a little bit of a gothic Barbie.
I feel like everyone
does a white wedding dress
and if you can pull off
a black wedding dress…
Shit, you can pull off anything.
And I can.
Oh my gosh.
[Heather gasps]
-Oh my gosh!
-[Christine] It's so heavy.
[Kara] It's a lot of volume,
and it's a lot of weight.
It's full sparkle.
-What do you think about it?
-[Christine] I think it's really pretty.
-Your boobs look amazing.
-[Christine] Thank you. I know. [laughs]
This'll make a statement
walking down the aisle.
[Christine] Yeah, but I might have
a seizure if I look at it too long,
-I'm just being honest. It's a lot.
-It is…
Okay. But we like the volume?
We like the ball gown?
-Dramatic silhouette.
-[Christine] Definitely love dramatics.
-Yes!
-[Kara laughs] Love the dramatics.
Oh my God. Don't fall, please.
[Christine] Oop! I'm sorry. [laughs]
-It's a fun one to try, for sure.
-It is really fun.
Could hide 4 kids under there
-or something.
-I know.
My perfect wedding dress would be
something sexy and sleek, maybe silky,
low-cut with maybe
a little light sparkle at the top, but…
still no ring.
[laughs nervously]
We keep thinking it might happen.
The big surprise.
No, I know he's not gonna--
he's gonna do it when I least expect it.
[clears throat]
[clears throat louder, laughs]
-You like it?
-[Heather] Oh my gosh.
-[Kara] Doesn't she look amazing?
-Holy moly.
[Kara] This will definitely be the styling
vibe you're going for for reception.
-I can see your ass. And I like it.
-[Christine] I know. You like it?
-[all laugh]
-Oh my God, I'm obsessed!
I know. Yeah, it's gorgeous.
I feel like we could do something…
a little more Maleficent vibes.
'Cause this is gonna be black.
See I love the mermaid, but it's not
dramatic enough, and I feel like
this would flow so much better
if we did something like ostrich feathers?
Oh God.
[Kara laughs]
-Oh!
-This one's really gorgeous.
-[Heather] I love it!
-[Christine] I love this one.
This is so beautiful.
[Christine] I love this dress.
I love it.
[Heather] Are you going
to Chrishell's charity event?
Every day I spend my life
with these bitches in the office.
I mean, like, that is the charity event.
[sighs]
[Heather] I think Amanza's going too.
How are you guys?
I don't know what her deal is.
I'm trying to clear the air with Mary,
but Amanza's just being
so passive-aggressive,
dramatic, rude.
Honestly, it's just, like, so aggressive,
unnecessarily so.
Why can't we just do
what the rest of us bitches do?
Which is we're nice to each other's face
and then talk shit behind our back.
Hey, I don't. Well, I guess
we are right now.
[Heather] Um, by the way,
this dress…
-You love it?
-…is absolutely stunning.
This is too much. I like it like that.
-Off the shoulder?
-[Christine] I like an off-the-shoulder
with floral, kind of, lace dripping down.
-I've got some soft black tulle--
-[Christine] Oh, perfect.
so the whole skirt would be made
out of something like this.
-Yes! Wow.
-[Kara] Which is so dramatic.
[Kara] So the whole thing would be black
with a little pop of sparkle.
-That's gorgeous.
-[Kara] Isn't that beautiful?
-Yeah, I love that.
-Stunning. I love this.
-So is this the one?
-Right? Is this your dress?
-I think it's your dress.
-I love it. It needs work, but--
For sure. Once we customize it,
and make it what you want,
-it's gonna be perfect.
-[Heather] So obsessed, I want one!
I want one!
-You'll have one very soon.
-[Heather] Very soon. I'm next.
-[Christine] I have a feeling.
-I'm next!
And spin.
♪ Spinning round and round ♪
[Heather laughs]
♪ So unbelievable ♪
♪ Didn't see it coming
No, you didn't see it coming ♪
♪ Every fall will take you breath ♪
This is nice.
Really cute little neighborhood.
-Hello?
-[Maya] Hey, guys.
-Hi! How are you?
-Welcome to ninety-two one oh.
[all laugh]
I pulled some strings and I got my clients
into this beautiful home
before it hits the market.
People love exclusive listings.
They wanna see something
that no one else knows about it
and no one else can have.
I know the listing agent on that one,
-so that's how we have the…
-[James] Oh, perfect.
…you know, sneak peak for it.
So it's gonna hit the market in,
I think, three weeks.
-[James] Great.
-Well thanks for showing it to us.
I might not have
a nine million dollar client like Mary's,
but I have a four million dollar client.
I may not have whales in my database
but I have a couple of dolphins.
It's a four bedroom, five-and-a-half-bath,
and it's a little bit over 4000
square feet,
-so it's large.
-[James] I love the openness.
♪ I could do this all day ♪
♪ All day
Do this all day ♪
[Maya] I wanna show you
the kitchen.
-[Maya] Custom-made island--
-Cool.
This is beautiful.
I love the height of it too.
[Maya] Countertop is all beautiful marble.
-[James] Wonderful.
-[Caitlynde] Love the colors.
[Maya] So what I love about the backyard,
you obviously have the pool,
you have landscape,
-but yet it's still low maintenance.
-[James] Right.
-[Maya] Let's go see the upstairs.
-[James] Perfect.
-[Maya] To the left, your master bedroom.
-[James] Okay.
What a great space…
-[Maya] Yeah, it's large.
-… very open.
It looks like there's a little patio
off the bedroom here.
-And high ceilings.
-Yeah.
And you have a very large closet,
which I know you're gonna appreciate.
-[James laughs]
-Great.
-Wow, this is nice. It already has--
-This is great.
-all the built-ins in, so…
-The built-ins, yeah.
That makes a difference.
-[Maya] What do you guys think?
-I think it's fantastic.
It's a really spacious house.
I like how it's a traditional layout,
very open floor plan.
So that's really nice.
-And there's so much for us to do with it.
-Right.
We can really add our own personal touch.
We wanna just pull the trigger
and put an offer in.
So 4.2 is the asking.
-Right.
-[Maya] What are you comfortable with?
We were kind of thinking
four million dollars,
and see what the reaction is.
Since it's an off-market deal,
I would hope that my clients
will come in at full ask.
But you never know what's gonna happen.
I think as long as you have
a four in front of it,
I think it's very important.
And I think it's very attractive.
You know what?
Let me work on the contract,
I'll send it to you for signature,
and fingers crossed.
-Okay.
-Perfect.
["Gimme More" playing]
♪ On the count of one, two, three, four ♪
♪ You've got to gimme more… ♪
I do not do mornings very well.
-[Waiter] Enjoy.
-[Christine] Thank you.
Hi, babe! I got you some coffee.
I hope that's okay.
-Good to see you.
-You know me.
[Christine] I know. I know.
I am so dreading talking to Christine.
I have managed to avoid her
for the past couple weeks.
And can't really continue that, so…
[sighs] guess we have to sit down
and hash it out.
-How are you?
-Oh my goodness. I'm good.
I feel like it's been so long.
You and I haven't had a one-on-one.
I just wanted to catch up
'cause I'm getting married.
I don't wanna fight with you again.
I love you so much.
[sighs] I don't know exactly what happened
and why,
but I do want it to change.
I just don't know
where all of this is coming from.
We tried to have a conversation,
we tried to talk it through,
and then I find out
you call me a fucking idiot.
I didn't say you were an idiot,
I said "acting."
Just because I was frustrated personally,
and I took it out on you.
-Right.
-So, that was my bad.
I don't want this in my life.
It just feels like you're so angry at me.
It's always been really hard
to talk to you.
Especially… now that Amanza's
joined the brokerage officially.
She's always there
and she's always protecting you,
and I'm trying to have a conversation
then she'll cut me off.
I feel like she's trying to drive a wedge
between me and you. It's making it so hard
-for me to be friends with you.
-I mean, Amanza's been in my life
for a long time, you know that. I don't
speak up a lot, I just kinda pull back.
And Amanza is obviously,
she's more kind of, like, how you are
where it's like,
if you have something to say, you say it.
And so she just comes to my defense.
Like, she just protects me.
My whole thing is
that I learned you don't defend Mary
'cause it won't get you anywhere.
I know.
-[Mary] Yeah, don't defend me.
-I know.
Well, let's just you and I start over
and try to get back to our friendship.
Just please, give her a chance.
I think it's really important
that you and Amanza kinda hash this out.
We're all in the office, we all hang out,
and now that you and I are hopefully back,
close again.
She's obviously been, like,
one of my best friends for 19 years,
-so she's not going anywhere.
-No, I totally understand it.
I just need her to back off, do my thing,
and just have etiquette, you know.
I mean, like, just need her
to get out of my way.
I just wanna be friends with you.
[Christine] I want everything
between us to be
back to the way things were.
I don't wanna fight either.
You're kinda a scary bitch,
and I don't wanna…
I am a scary bitch, right?
Yeah, I know. I really am.
I'm a fucking crazy bitch.
But you're an awesome crazy bitch, though.
-Cheers to crazy.
-Cheers to that.
I can't believe
you're getting married in a church.
-I know.
-Are you're allowed in?
It's gonna burn up when I walk in,
trust me.
["Make It Look Easy" playing]
♪ Gonna show you what I'm all about now
Gonna show you all the things I do ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't stop the rhythm
When it's flowing through me and you ♪
♪ I'm a money money money money maker ♪
Oh my God, these cupcakes…
♪ Just watch what I can do ♪
Chrishell.
-[Chrishell] Hey!
-[Mary] How are you?
-Oh, you look so pretty! Hi!
-You do too.
-[Chrishell] Good to see you!
-You too. You got the flip-flop memo, huh?
[Chrishell] Yes! You know,
it's a lot of running around before we…
-get started.
-[Amanza] Knock, knock.
-[Chrishell] Oh, hi!
-I wore my fancy shoes.
-[Chrishell] Yes! We got the memo!
-[Amanza] I look like a mall walker.
[Amanza] So I have--
My friend has a candle company
and so this is a description
of what they all are.
-[Chrishell] Wonderful!
-These smell so good.
[Amanza] And I brought a couple to light
so they can smell them.
Amanza, that's so sweet!
What time is it? 5:38?
-[Chrishell] Okay heel-time!
-5:38.
[Amanza] I should put my shoes on, too.
[Chrishell] They're pretty to look at,
but not great to walk in.
[Mary] Maybe I should not have put
these shoes on when I'm carrying a chair.
-[Chrishell] We put them on too early!
-[Mary] I'm gonna fall.
-[Chrishell] Where'll we put these chairs?
-[Amanza] 'Cause I was like a dope.
-Hang on. Okay, I got it.
-[Chrishell] Where we--?
I'm talking to Kate.
She's trying to help me stage a condo.
[Mary] What?
[Chrishell] It looks very good.
[Mary] Um… I don't know
if Romain's coming tonight.
-[Chrishell] He's not coming?
-I don't know. For a couple  reasons.
First, I don't know if I want him here.
I'm really mad at him. Really mad.
What happened?
He didn't do anything
really, really, like, bad,
but he lied about something
about the bachelor party.
And so now, I'm just, like… pissed.
I just found out that Romain lied to me
about his bachelor party in Vegas.
I had one rule.
Don't bring girls up to the hotel room.
There's only one reason
why you bring girls up to the room.
Of course,
Brett and Jason, they bring the girls up.
This is actually
a very sensitive subject to me.
I've been cheated on, I've been lied to.
My ex-boyfriend, right before Romain,
was the biggest douchebag ever.
He, like, cheated, was on dating apps
while we lived together.
He was just horrible.
So I'm traumatized by that.
I never thought I had to worry
about anything like that with Romain.
So this is just, like, a little…
brings up those feelings.
And I don't like it.
-When it's not such a madhouse--
-What're you talking about?
-you'll give me the full… dish.
-[Amanza] Christine?
-[Mary] No, I told her who it was, but…
-Do you already know?
-[Mary] Yeah. Christine's coming, right?
-[Chrishell] I think so.
Great. I brought a giant wedge
to give her. [laughs]
So Mary told me
that Christine thinks I'm driving a wedge
between their friendship,
which is so fucking stupid
because Mary and I have been
best friends for twenty years.
And I don't understand
how I can be driving a wedge
in the middle of a friendship
that isn't really existing right now.
Chrishell's a one-stop shop.
We've got This Is Us,
Young and the Restless, Days of Our Lives.
I know. I was like, okay,
who can I get prizes from?
Me, my husband, and my best friend?
-Hi!
-[Chrishell] Hi!
-I like it, it's open.
-[Chrishell] You look so gorgeous!
-I'm showing a little bit.
-[Chrishell] You're not. You're gorgeous.
[Maya] Wow, this is great, Chrishell.
Oh, this looks pretty.
[Davina] So pretty!
Yay!
-Hi!
-[Davina] Hi!
[Heather] This is cool.
[Chrishell] Make yourself at home,
get a drink.
So this is your new listing?
-Yes. It just got staged.
-Yes!
[Mary] That's cute.
[Chrishell] You wanna see
what our donation items are?
Obviously, you know,
we have the Laker tickets.
-This is an Annie Leibovitz signed poster.
-Wow.
And coffee with Justin Hartley.
-[guest] Okay.
-This is my husband, by the way.
-[guest] Awesome.
-Hi, guys.
Oh, there's Christine.
Is that Marilyn Monroe?
[Amanza groans] She has issues.
-Hi! How are you?
-[Chrishell] How are you?
-[Christine] This is great of you!
-You look gorgeous! How are you?
-Good.
-You look beautiful. This is so fun!
[Amanza] I'm just gonna sit over here
and be quiet. [laughs]
How are you? Good to see you.
-[Mary] Thank you.
-This looks so nice.
So these are all the items
that you're bidding off?
Yes. So feel free to go shopping.
[pop music playing]
♪ Tick, boom uh-oh ♪
[Amanza] Is this a wedge of cheese?
[Mary] You are too funny.
Is this a wedge of cheese?
Would you call that a wedge of cheese?
- Christine, is this a wedge of cheese?
-[Christine] A wedge.
I don't understand
what Amanza's trying to accomplish
with these lame dad jokes,
but the way she's acting towards me
is just not the time and place for this.
I mean, have some etiquette.
[Chrishell] Romain's here.
[Chrishell] Just so you know.
-[Chrishell[ Hi, how are you?
-Hey. How are you?
-[Romain] Hello. How are you?
-Hi. Good, how are you?
Hello, bestie. Mary, you're driving
a wedge between Romain and I's friendship.
[Amanza laughs]
-[Mary] Sorry.
-[Amanza] Yeah.
[Jason] You're driving a wedge
between me and sleep.
-[Amanza] Who? Her?
-[Brett] And me and sleep.
Me. Oh, 'cause I was on the phone with him
last night. Yelling.
-I'm glad I didn't pick up.
-[repeating] Fuck you.
That's all I have to say
to anybody right now.
-[Heather] Everyone looks so pretty.
-[Christine] Everyone looks like sluts.
-I like Amanza's velvet dress.
-Me too.
-I don't.
-Christine keeps looking at me.
And, I'm just annoyed.
Hi, Micky! Looks great, right?
[repeating] Yeah, I love it.
[Amanza] I feel like a Christmas tree.
-Like I have a bulb on top.
-You don't look it.
I closed Willaman today.
-Nice! Good job.
-[Amanza] Look at you!
-[Jason] Good job. Is that four million?
-Four million.
The owner accepted my Willaman offer.
It's a nice commission right there.
I didn't think he was going to accept
because we offer below asking,
but hey, I'm not gonna complain.
Does that mean
you'll give me a listing now?
-Or not get my hopes up?
-I won't make money if I reciprocate
-every sale with one of my own listings.
-Wait, I want a listing.
Sorry, I'm not gonna ask anymore.
I can sell
the most expensive property in LA,
and Jason still
will not give me a listing.
Sweetheart, this is Katya.
I think you've met?
-[Chrishell, Katya] Nice to meet you!
-[Brett] She's gonna donate this. Can we…
[Chrishell] This is lovely.
[Christine] Katya looks like
if me and you had a baby.
-Right? Like our baby.
-[Mary] Yeah.
And we got a really good nose job
and good fillers.
-[Davina] That's hilarious.
-[Heather] Oh my gosh.
-[Heather] Where is she?
-[Christine] Crazy, right? Behind you.
[Maya] Oh, I want to talk to you.
'Cause you have your broker's license.
I'm starting to study
for my broker's license in Florida.
I'm gonna spend more time in Miami
once the second kid comes.
Well, that makes sense.
I don't know if I'm going to get
full support from Jason.
I mean, I suggested him to--
As far as
getting a broker's license in Florida?
-Yeah.
-Really?
-Would it be an Oppenheim Group office?
-I don't know. You know, it depends.
Like, I'm going back and forth.
Like, I love Jason's marketing.
Yeah, me too.
The only thing that sometimes
rubs me the wrong way is, like,
the unbalanced, you know, favoritism.
You know, Jason favorites Mary.
But, I want to ask you,
like, you got your broker's license.
Obviously, you're still with Jason.
Are you sometimes thinking,
why do I even need this?
I should do my own thing?
It certainly crosses my mind, you know?
-Oh my gosh.
-Hi, boo-boo. Can I talk with you quick?
[Amanza] Yeah. Shall I fill my glass
for this conversation? [laughs]
I deal with shit face-to-face.
Amanza's bullshit is not my vibe,
and I'm about to call her out on it.
I just feel like you've been…
super awkward to me, like…
-I walked in and you snubbed me.
-[Amanza] Tonight? Yeah.
[Amanza] I snubbed you
when you walked in because…
I had a conversation with Mary,
and I didn't like what I heard.
And so, I'm super annoyed.
I feel like there is a competition
about who is better friends with Mary.
[Davina] The main thing is
that Mary doesn't seem to care.
-So, like, why--?
-Mary never cares.
-Yeah, so--
-Everybody fight about Mary.
I feel like it's been hard because
you've been in the middle a little bit.
I'm driving a wedge
between you and Mary's friendship?
It's just really, really hard
to talk to her.
When have you tried to talk to her
that I didn't allow you to?
Well, the wedding was one.
[Christine] The wedding
was really, really difficult.
I talked to you
for 3 seconds at the wedding.
I definitely, a million percent,
do not remember that.
-Stop lying. Stop!
-You never did. At your birthday party--
-You're ridiculous.
- … you called me a liar.
Stop with your games.
-This is exhausting.
-Really? I don't know,
maybe it's because I have
important shit going on in my life
that's stressful
and I don't, like, remember
little, petty, drama,
high school, girlfriend comedy.
Do you think that no one else
has stressful stuff going on?
Maybe it affects me differently.
I don't remember things like that.
So how about this. I won't be snubby…
but, like, maybe just…
try to be a little more…
nice, you know?
Alright. Well…
It's been real, Christine.
Okay. Real annoying.
-[Davina] Hey.
-Hi.
-[Davina] How's it going over there?
-It was like my IQ was going down
just being in that situation.
I know this is a charity event,
I'm like, this is charity,
by me, like, sitting here.
Like, I should be bidding on this.
Bon voyage.
["Devil Inside" playing]
♪ You all got a little bit
Of devil inside ♪
♪ Uh oh oh oh
Uh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Tearing you apart
In the middle of the night ♪
♪ Uh oh oh oh
Uh oh oh oh ♪
♪ You all got a little bit
Of devil inside ♪
If you wanna get your bids in, we're gonna
close the bidding in 15 minutes.
Why doesn't it say how many tickets?
I don't understand.
♪ Uh oh oh oh
Uh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Tearing you apart
In the middle of the night ♪
[funky music playing]
♪ Turn their heads around ♪
So Fennell, let's talk open house.
I picked out the artwork.
I hope you like it.
I don't know what the staging looks like,
-so I just kind of, like--
-Blindly?
[Heather] Yeah. Everything in there
was beautiful,
everything was very, like,
pop and bright and colors.
So I hope that goes with the staging.
Heather did me a really big favor
by going and choosing the art
because I had to be at court that day.
But if it doesn't match,
that's gonna delay us, which could
essentially screw us with the timeline.
And that will suck.
You talking about Fennell?
-I wanna hear.
-Yeah. She couldn't make it that day,
so she was in charge of the staging,
and everything,
-but I went and got the art and--
-She hasn't seen the staging,
I haven't seen the art.
We don't know what…
[Amanza] The color palette's
very California modern.
It's white, like, a little bit of black,
but then very neutral.
Okay. So I went with a lot of color.
So you're telling me...
you have artwork the same color
as Christine's shoes in the house?
-[Amanza] You got pink artwork?
-Yes. It's pink, but not that pink.
Most of these buyers are men
in the Hollywood Hills.
I actually blew up my centerfold,
my Playboy photo.
-[Davina] Oh, wow.
-[Heather] I put it above the fireplace.
[Jason] That's very male--
I think that'd work well.
[Amanza] That'd probably sell the house,
actually.
Actually, that would be cute.
[Amanza] That's a good idea.
Give me some ideas.
This is going south, quick.
No, honestly. I'm very girly,
so I went in with, like,
what would Heather like? But--
-Why'd you do that? You're not the buyer.
-[Maya] What are you gonna list it for?
Three point six-nine-nine.
I might bring my clients
to the broker's open.
[Christine repeating] Guys.
-What is it?
-I just got a Google alert from TMZ.
About what?
"Justin Hartley files for divorce."
[Mary] No.
[Maya] What? No fucking way.
-It's all over the Internet right now.
-[Heather] No way.
No way.
[Maya] Let me see.
This isn't real.
She was totally fine.
We just were with her.
Oh my God, that poor girl.
But what happened?
Like, how come someone just files?
[Heather] July eighth?
-[Mary] Hang on, I'm gonna call her.
-[phone dials]
[over phone] Hi,
you've reached Chrishell--
[Heather] It doesn't make sense…
It makes me feel sick.
She's not answering, guys.
[Mary] Oh my God.
["Without You" playing]
♪ Without you ♪
♪ Ooo… ♪